sumolounge.com 2016-05-06

# Online Bean Bags | Sumo Lounge Privacy Policy

**SumoLounge.com Privacy Policy**  

At SumoLounge.com we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information.

**Personal Information and Other Data we Collect**

SumoLounge.com collects personal information when you register for our site or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.

SumoLounge.com uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our services.

SumoLounge.com servers automatically record information when you visit our website, including, but not limited to the URL, IP address, browser type, language, and the date and time of your request.

**Uses of this Data**

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. In addition we may use this information to improve our services.

**We may share your information with:**

Service providers under contract who help with parts of our business operations, such as fraud prevention, bill collection, marketing, and technology services. We may share your information with service providers who assist us with serving relevant ads to you. We require by contract that our service providers only use your information in connection with the services they perform for us and not for their own benefit.

We may share aggregated non-identifiable information with Publishers or our Advertisers, such as the number of users who visit a Publisher website or the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisement. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of the website publishers that you visit to learn about their data collection practices. We do not provide information to our Advertisers about your activities. However, when you view or interact with a Retargeted ad, the Advertiser may infer that you engaged in the activities on its site that qualified you to receive the ad.

Other third parties with your consent or direction to do so.

We may share information about you if necessary to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of Sumo Lounge or others.

**How we protect personal information**

We employ reasonable and appropriate security measures such as maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable security requirements, including US federal and state regulations. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption; we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files; and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities. All credit card information is encrypted before it is transmitted across the network. However, no security system is foolproof and we cannot guarantee the security of your information.

**Your choices**

We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible.

You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result.

We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible.

You may use the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) **opt out tool**. We also comply with the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising as managed by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). You may opt out via the DAA website at  **http://www.aboutads.info/choices/**.

**How you can contact us about privacy questions**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact support@sumolounge.com or write to us at the address below.

If you are located in the European Economic Area, Sumo Lounge International is the entity responsible for the processing of your personal information. To exercise your rights of access, rectification, blocking, or deletion or to object to the processing of your personal information, contact support@sumolounge.com or write to us at:

Sumo Lounge International  
8350 Wilshire Boulevard

Los Angeles, CA 90211 

1-866-340-7866
